I'm not sure if you probably saw it, you know.
And it'll continues, you know, I guess Alexandra went over to to betas, you know, right after striking me for a video with my, you know, information in it, you know, so we'll see how that goes, right.
But, um, yeah, so, um, yeah, but beta wouldn't let anybody up or, you know, if you're just listening out, I guess, you know, it's like, you know, I mean, it's like if someone's actively being attacked, and allegations are being made and stuff, I would let them up at the same time.
I guess, you know, she's a difficult yeah
Yeah, she yeah, she's she's on the strike strike strike thing
So I got to get those those privacy complaints filed, right? But um
Yeah, and oh my gosh, you know beat it. I guess their friends, you know, I mean it's so funny
I know she didn't bought dogs be his family and you know and be his name and stuff
I you know be that that's all it's all in the past all forgiven because they can hate bond over me
They can hate bond over, you know crystalline and you know, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you know
So if I if I go out of this thing, you know
Whatever, you know, I mean, I'll be back, you know, but uh, we'll see we'll just see we'll see
See what happens, right? But uh, yeah, it's pretty amazing pretty amazing
You know
So I thought I'd let you know give a chance to respond if anybody that wasn't given a chance over there to
To their side of the story. I was actually just in the chat
And then a person said no cat chokers allowed
So again, I'm being accused of animal abuse and hidden and Chad's not given
You know, I let Bita talk for a long time in my chat yesterday calling me all kind of ship
before apparently had enough of it, but all I was doing was responding to to
You know that that monster other two monsters, you know
I was doing was responding, but you know in a purse that person's terrible and oh Nancy were banned, too
You know I met I met Nancy and be this chat probably about a year and a half ago
you know, that's where I met Nancy and
You know we know be the turned against her because she thought the thing that is was talking behind the scenes with her
And I guess beat is just very possessive and also, you know, yeah
Where the ogres of my thumbnail that's beta on the left and that is alexandra mayors, you know
This is like gonna know they are it is kind of photorealistic
Well, at least the beta one is I just typed in kind of like, you know tall black lady for the alexandra
And it came up came out pretty accurate, but uh, yeah
Yeah, the beta one. Yep
You know what did this didn't sound like eighth grade Sharon?
What me or over there? I mean did you hear we rap beat us when when Alice came up and
Started started spouting off and now she's a yeah
You know they got Rick Rick who's some chat, you know son died of cancer, you know
Attacking him
Alexandra said she's already over her father's death which you know with that
she wasn't saying that the other day she was just saying I was manipulating her
and she didn't seem to care and she said oh she said two years is enough time
because that's how much time I've had with my father's death but two years is
enough time she said but you know
You know so but I guess you know she said today she's like oh, she's like she's like I'm over that she's over that
She's like oh, you know so Rick should get over it right and like you know
Pretty sick pretty sick and the actual people died actually actually actually taking my father over there
Yeah, I'm not sure. Yeah, I'm sorry. I actually taking my father's photo
I don't know if you've seen that one where she took my father's photo and put some you know
Lizard lizard skin on him and and a tail the thing was my mom
She did that you know Vita doesn't have a problem with that. Yeah, that's like a three over there
They're like no that poor poor thing that is is being like, you know
You know attacked by people and you know, I mean he even he was threatened by Alexander speaking up
She's talking about she's getting all these death threats and stuff like that. Yeah
Amazing amazing. You know when I played the death threat. She's made against me. She several several death threats
but anyway
Then Christine saying that it's fine. There's no karma for hurting me. There's no jail time because you know, I'm it's I'm the problem, right?
Yeah, yeah, it's just like yeah, so sorry Sharon. I didn't mean to like it. I'm a little bit
You know a little bit because what triggered or something like that from from just having to listen to that that just a garbage, you know
that
I guess and she's turning on crystal and I guess what beat is clean beat is clean
She a beat it beat it has absolutely nothing all the stuff that Alexander said about beta everything all all the you know
Over a year of her going after her that was oops. Oopsy. Oops. It was just a mistake because you're clean beta
Wow
And the beta is going up to the content. I mean beta just not even challenging anything. I mean, okay
Just basically give her the red carpet
I mean, it's one thing when I had her on my show
because we were friends at the time, you know?
Yeah, she's clean according to Alex, yeah.
So whoops, I guess, Bida, your family doesn't own slaves
in Iran like she was saying,
but I mean, I mean, she's kind of so sure about it.
It is so fake, isn't it fake?
Isn't it so disgusting?
You know and then doxing me on this over on beta saying my last name and stuff media didn't even correct her
They don't say that going she brought up children. She brought big troll his daughter and stuff like that
No, no response from beta beta ignoring the chat beta not letting anybody else on that crystal
And the people that were still active not Rick not
People are actively having
Stuff said about them right then. No, they can't respond
And they're not even in chat, you know, I can't even talk in the chat because person says I'm an animal abuser and you know
Beta has no problem with me being hidden for for that, right? Like for that false accusation
Hmm. I mean
Even I with the whiskers thing. I was like, well, I mean, I can't even believe it
I mean, it's I just hope that it's there. I'm not I'm seeing things right now
I'm just hope that I'm hallucinating with what I say. I'm even I can't even I mean it was I couldn't even watch that is so hard
Just even think it's like that's the thing. It's like oh
It's like that's I mean, I'm just so sick and I can't even like think about that and recall animal abuser for my casters
I'm like my children
My beta my beta is now beta saying it, you know beta says it now
You'd think she would know better. I mean, I've even been a beater throughout this stupid whisker thing and and all this stuff and I know
But she comes on she and Sam and come on doing a double team. Oh this and this and this oh
Yeah, oh, where's your cats? Where's the cats cats? He knows don't run an animal run away, right?
Hmm. I mean, it's it's it's crazy. It is really crazy
Um, yeah, I mean, I can listen to that they have omate just talking about he's the same thing that it likes just like suck his own dick and
drink his own common stuff and and like
They say that because I love my cats to get to me. I know I know
But you know what the thing is people don't get that people don't like most people don't see that and they'll just believe
What she says because they're like followers, right?
They're just uh, you know, I don't care if people don't
Like life me. I'll talk to them still and stuff like that
I'm not gonna make accusations like that against them and like, you know
Like they would do to me because I'm not that low
I'm uh, I have a heart, you know
Which is why I hold back so much with the immersion I have I hold back a lot, you know
But you know the more you push on me the more you push on me and keep going on me is like that
I will I will start to talk more, you know, yeah
Yeah, that poor with that person is just horrible person was in my chat
I was always nice to first I never did anything to person person just turned on me because beaded it you like to stay
Meeting with everyone, but it's getting so mean and hurtful, right?
You've watched so many streamers get targeted but never seen those kind of hurtful comments. I know it's getting so disgusting
It's getting so disgusting
And they're changing the game and for the for the worst, you know, they're ruining basically the oh here's that we have a guess
Okay, yeah, they're ruining basically the the whole streaming community for everybody
And, you know, when it goes away or when it just is like, you know, so disgusting, no one wants to be, you know, anymore, you can blame them.
I mean, they're bringing in this attitude. Here you go. Here's the link.
Yeah. And, you know, they're attacking Karen and, you know, I hope Rick comes over here.
And I want Rick to tell us out of the story if he wants you too, because, you know, I, yeah, we have a guest.
Hey, yeah, I saw a lot of that garbage and a friend that knows about all this called me and said
You know just stay out of it. I started making a video
But beta is a liar because I show proof like Alex said to her I always show receipts
I haven't talked to Rick the last time I talked to him was right after I came out of the hospital
And I talked to him briefly.
He never said, fuck you or anything.
You know, we had a talk and I just decided that, you know,
he was still going at Carissa and using Zaya.
And I was just sick of it because all he did was and I have everything I keep everything
I have his text where he's sending me stuff on Carissa
Call her job call this call wherever she was training. I didn't call any of those places and I wasn't going to
That's all he does. He did the same thing about Alex before he was he's the one that sent a picture of her sitting
With an afro and with a sign saying that she need I don't know it was weird
No, they didn't have a I then I don't know it didn't look like it had to be fake because you know these people can make fake pictures
Because I don't think she was ever on the streets holding a sign like that
So I can show it came from him though. Yeah
Yeah, I'm Kiwi Farmer that says that she was, um, you know, staying with her mother and her sister
and she was kicked out and she was homeless and then she went to move with her dad. So she was
homeless for a period and so I know about that. Oh, she's doing good then. You know, if she was
homeless and, you know, I mean, shit, and I don't have to worry about anything. I come from money
and everybody knows that. I mean, that's why I got to live all over the world and my mom's dad was a politician.
and she was engaged to Goni who became president of Bolivia in 93 and I had to be the one to tell
him that she passed away and I don't remember I'd never met the man and he knew of me and he said
well you were actually born on my birthday I said when's your birthday and July 1st he said
and and and then I told him about my siblings he said oh I didn't know you had siblings I just knew
of you and that when your mom was said she was pregnant with you I told her that
you know, come to Bolivia and I'd raise you as my own. She told me that. But yeah, so I don't
have to worry about shit. So I'm not going to let this bother me like it did. I'm not on drugs
anymore. It started to get me triggered until a friend of mine that was involved with these people,
she called me and she said, Karen, don't get triggered, don't react, don't react.
She she talked me down from it. Yeah, because black our Jesus the chat is saying. Oh, I annex is 350 pounds
I just want to say I've seen I annex on camera. She's not 300 feet pounds. She's no not at all
And that's Steven and that's who's kiwi farms once and so I'm giving him the his information
So yeah, he can go to hell. He's a coward and he's on the clip where he said yeah
Yeah, and then he was promoting his podcast. So I sent that to kiwi
I but she I mean she Alice was going after him in the chat
and she was going after you, she was going after me,
she was going after Crystal.
But she said, Bita's clean.
She says she has Bita, absolutely nothing.
I mean, I guess all the time she was attacking Bita,
I guess it was over nothing
because she said Bita's totally clean.
Bita's done nothing.
How's Bita clean?
She said a lot of stuff.
She sent me this court information in 2024 about Alex
and told me to go to the court house
and give him that information on her
because she got it from Amber.
Oh, wow.
Oh, wow. So it was some serious stuff. I still have it. Yeah. I save everything. Yeah. Yeah. And that's why it's good that you save everything. Yeah. Yeah. I have a you know, I save it to my hard drives. I have extras and I and everything I had on my other computer. I have it in the extra hard drive that I get because I get a bunch of those for movies and stuff that I download that I keep.
Yeah, I mean like that one that me to where she's busted saying something she was shocked that I had it.
Now I said, Vita, you're lying to me, because look at this.
Here you're telling your two ex-friends,
let's have Karen go after Barb and Ella.
Okay.
And Eldo saw it, and he said,
well, that sounds like Vita and Crystal lied,
and she said, well, no, Amy, I don't think it was Vita.
She knew it was.
Yeah, well, again, I was on Crystal's last night.
Crystal let me up, and Crystal, I mean, I was like,
you know, she wasn't, she wasn't,
Very nice, but she was completely completely mean and she let me up for as long as I wanted to be up. I guess but
Yeah, now a gamble is saying. Oh, well, you know crystals flooding psyche up to bother Bita and stuff like that
Can I show Bita's pick? Yeah, I can show be this picture
Hold on a second because you know Bita has no problem going after me calling me cat abuser and all this stuff
And so we do have this
You know, we did this one that I've gotten from some place.
Well, they said that about her cats.
Yeah, that is her real picture.
It came on when she was yelling at a Q45
and he put it on his profile picture.
And they made fun of her and that he went at her on on Skelly's
and Skelly let him do that.
And then Fisher got on and went at her.
But yeah, this is where it came on by accident.
You can never clear a picture where
it shows the skin tags around her eyes.
Yeah.
Yeah
That is a real one twack that is a real picture that is a real that is a real picture her cam came on
She didn't have makeup on it was late at night
Yeah, her face looks like that and I have another picture of her
it's more clear because she complained about skin tags around her eyes and
I'll send it to you. She it's clear that she has skin tags right around both eyes like around the under the eyebrows
But over the lid of her eyes and then below that too and crystal said yes
She her ex-friend said that yes
She had it and you know that people get it because something about the skin and she was trying to get it fixed
I guess they can get it fixed. I don't know
Okay to act go to grateful 26. There's a video with the more pictures of beta like another picture of beta where she's bald
That's why she's so mad. Yeah, she went nuts
Yeah, she has the bald spot on the top of the head on one side and that's why she puts combs over her hair like that
You know do
have that. But yeah, so
she always told me, y'all
you tell the truth. Yeah,
I've always done that. An
the in real life for the
hated him and everything.
And we were with a group of people that we know, and he knew what he said was he said the one thing about Karen is that she always tells the truth because even if she's involved in it anyway, she'll bust herself to and that's true.
I'm telling the truth. I did it. You know, you did this too.
I've never seen I never known you to I mean everything that you said is checked out and you have received about it.
And that's why he was saying he said she always shows proof and it's like we do real life
I was surprised he said that because me and him went at it a few times in real life
And he'd lie about stuff
But for him to say that I was surprised that he said that one thing about Karen and she always tells the truth
And I was surprised it was like damn coming from him
So, I always do. I always feel I have to. I show proof. That's why I've been on the news media sometimes
because I do show proof. I have my phone and camera and I've caught some things.
And I was on the news media a couple of times over it. And especially on the rescue of a cat,
I had pictures and they came in and got the cat from that guy. I mean, he was abused on
He doesn't love a person and I was typing in Vita's chat about like a little bit about Alex
I had Alex talks my family and then a person hid me and person said oh no cat chokers allowed
And so you know Vita obviously has no problem with me being slandered in the chat with no no right to defend myself
You know so I mean that's just it's pretty sad. You know I'm pretty sad
Yeah, it's just it's better to stay away like that friend gave me good advice because me and her used to go at it and she was good friends with Gia.
I showed Gia's last communication with me. We were cool. She hated crystal and did a a discord chat, you know, it was titled. Let's get crystal 51 50 and Bob was there.
You know and I have done and I found the proof on it because she said oh
I was never in a group about the 5150 and I just laughed to myself because it's like I haven't on my computer
Because you were all in there and yeah afraid of me then because
She was saying it was a fake person imitate like why would there be a fake person back then like when she wasn't even known
I mean, it's like no, it's a it's them in there. It's it's a group chat. It's it's images videos, you know
And it's yeah, I have it she doesn't she doesn't know that I have that
So I remember she was scared of me and she wouldn't say much and me and Vita were going at it.
Yeah, it's good. And then the other truth is,
Yeah, Alex never sent Brandon a thousand dollars. I thought maybe he was telling the truth and then he said 4,000
So now he's trying to come at me
We know he is he lies and you know
And he doesn't let it go he keeps he gets obsessive and he thinks crystal and gamble are done for good
No, she hates him because yesterday on her life. She said that
Brandon because she hates petals and she that's one of the reasons we had a falling out again because I talked to him and she was
Trying to make me not talk to him and you even said it
You know she talks him because of that petal Brandon. Yeah
They like W. Crystal. Oh Crystal, you know, he greets her now
Oh, no, she can't stand them because she says he's a petal. She never liked him. Yeah
You know, but yeah, so I'm just gonna stay away and I appreciate the reality Nancy. She commented
She could use her account. I don't think I have her hidden or anything
Okay, yeah, and when Noel comes around why don't you interview her cuz I'm not a person who interviews because she
All right, well, I'm gonna go ahead and yeah, I'm gonna
Okay, love you too. You have a good day. Okay. Okay. Bye. Bye. Bye
Yeah, and so we're you know, we're getting like the we're getting like the true sides of the story now
You know, it's like I really am about the truth and it's like that's you know
Really even if I look bad in some things, you know, because I'm not perfect person either
But I'm certainly not an animal abuser. I'm certainly not you know
And as for like these things would be the same thing doxy and stuff
Yeah, okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry Sharon, you know, it's like, you know, I mean not everyone's gonna like everybody
But you know, you know, we had she you know, because having Alex up, you know, uninterrupted
Making accusations and stuff. I did want her to have a chance to
depend on yourself and
So what you wanted to say and same with you if you want to come up
You know you're welcome to show your experience too because I know Sharon was once you know
I met Sharon and Alex's chat is an Alex mod and stuff. Yeah
and you know as you know like she does everybody turn on her and you know and these are people that you know
Just like she turned on me, you know a couple times
I think be it was like well didn't you like you know weren't you like didn't you weren't you?
didn't she like accept Psyche's apology back in April or something and it kind of got glossed over.
Yeah, so I'll give like a little timeline of events. I think I met Alexandra last year
when she came to my chat and we had a great conversation and it was a time and I think like,
you know, I think maybe she don't she gave me a hundred bucks after that show or something like
that, you know, she and it was like, wow, you know, this is somebody that understands like my
that things I have talent and, you know, all kinds of,
we had some good conversations and for three months
we were friends and we actually met in person.
She came and drove over one night and took me to dinner.
I always would say, you know, she was very generous,
you know, the gifts.
And things like that and then in December we were supposed to do this holiday extravaganza kind of thing and
All of a sudden one day she posted this AI art of me that said like oh, I went with psyche dreams about it
And it was my cats all with these big bags of money
Like I was out dirty on the couch and the cats were just walking all over me
And I said a weird feeling about it like just didn't it just rub me the wrong way
And so I wrote her and I said are you turning against me? I like everyone else because
you know
Then I'm just gonna quit YouTube and I didn't get back to her for a day
But then by the next day she had said, you know, you know
No, don't never talk to me again blow up and then she started posting
These memes on her show me burning in the dumpster with the Sandman and beta burning me in the dumpster
She posted me sir posted me like really bald out now
It gets like where I'm just like so disgustingly bald and ugly and just like deformed and
Got a cat on my shoulder
Uh, you know, like, you know, which I love, I love when the cat gets in my shoulder, but it turns into like some kind of like, like weird, you know, anything that, you know, I treasure, it's like kind of like trying to trash it, but she's been, I think the furthest it went was when she posted like me and like, like an ice cream truck, and then she had like a, like a, like a child joker and a child.
Benny Blanco, I guess, and was then coming to Psyche's Playhouse or something like that.
By that, and then she started posting me with me having sex with Tommy James and stuff like that.
And by that point, it was just so ridiculous. I wasn't sort of laughing. I thought it was kind
of silly at that point because nothing was, you know what she said in my last, my name and stuff
like that. But we, we actually reconciled, you know, she posted like something nice called
We became friends again and all of a sudden, you know, and she was also she was a very generous again
I never asked her for anything. It was always a surprise from sending flowers to me
From sending, you know, a fish taco one day for lunch. She sent me some cash apps
You know, I put her up on my my cold codex as like, you know, I advertised her channel had her up on the front page
I edited it, you know, so she would, in her profile, how she would like it and stuff like
that.
I just, I gave her almost full access and, and I did that.
And then, um,
You know the brand in huge situation when she got me pulled back into that stronger
You know, I didn't try to pull her into it. She did it to herself into the situation the reason that she
Got mad at me again when she was when Brandon turned against her then she said I
It was my fault somehow and I was trying to humiliate her by having her repart with Brandon or something like that
But then it started now. She's then she started doxing my mother my father
our family business our
You know the website
my apartment complex and you know encouraging people to harass me and and then she started
with the death threats and I never I never I don't threaten people I don't I mean it's like I
and especially though so but no but she has plenty of plenty of death threats are logged of her against
me with including Christine saying that she would have no karma no bad karma for hurting me
nor would she um face any jail time for her to be because I am such a bad person
Okay, and then Christine has an nerve to come in here and said leave Alex alone like I'm going after Alex or something like that
Yeah, so I mean it just gets so sick. Have I gotten any no I have not because you know what that that the group that does that
they had two indictments for cyber bullying and harassment and
so they've stopped doing most that stuff and
You know, which is good because you know
So yeah, I mean, I guess there was a couple a couple bags of concrete. I don't know
I don't know exactly who who sent those but there was yeah, it was like every last month. There was a couple bags
which just got you know given away and
Who were they? Well, we know they're called the kennel kickers, you know
And I will all say is like that I know that you know that Tony the conductor is their their fall person
Who they let and he's actually got it being one of the indictments
There's an actually another person that was indicted as well
But he had indictment for something else and yeah, and he stopped because you know now
They're probably watching him care very carefully because but you know the federal government is involved in this kind of thing
You know so obviously he's gonna like you know
Obviously too if they look into his records they can see all the text now numbers and they can see all the messages
Where he's directing people to my house to and on Christmas
I think I got like 30 bags of concrete and all that stuff right and you know
That's what started the problems my neighbors. I I didn't start it started
It was people attacking me and then she's saying
Oh, well. Oh, it's poor neighbors, you know, the guy who was so irritated he I woke him up
Or you know, I must have woken him up at night. It was 9 30. Yeah, they think text now is a run trace. Well, no
It's all IP address. It's all I mean now it goes back. They have down to where they are
So, you know, if the federal government starts getting involved, you know, you're fucked
You're basically you're fucked because all of it is all of it is uh, yeah
It was apparently some guy that a black guy that had gotten great or something like that and then they were laughing about that
I mean, it's like so
You know, I mean, I'm just gonna let the let the you know karma and the God and the law take care of all that
Because you know, obviously they've slowed their roll
But you can look up kennel kickers on
On QE farms and you can get the whole rundown you can get all about how they how they actually bullied
This guy Gary Chapin and they also bullied at one point the Tony the conductor
who was so desperate for friendship or something
that he kept trying to like, you know,
he drank toilet water, he microwaved his own cell phone
and all kinds of things to get in with them
and they never actually let them in, you know?
Yeah.
All the stuff about you if you listen to the streamer you can listen you can't listen to that streamer is yeah
Yeah, exactly Sharon exactly Sharon and yeah, and I know black black Archie has both the cameras on black Archie
Well, you're on that website too. You can look at black Archie. He's a feature on QE farms
You can get all the information they have about him
As well and what he does and everything he's also kind of like a lower in the hierarchy
I guess of the kennel kicker who was actually run by some guy with an in 007
But it's all on there. Just search kennel kickers on QE farms. You can read the whole thing
There's a whole thread about it
And all the stuff they've done to other people right and RG is a snitch. He's a little bitch
He's amazing and run back and forth and you know
But does he have any information about himself out?
No, I don't know if he's that person,
the cocaine on person or whatever.
It does sound like him.
It does look like him.
He doesn't have the same dog, but who knows?
He always, he obviously is maybe bothered by that.
If someone said, for example,
like Brandon's already coming in here
and he's sort of posting an address and everything,
it wasn't my address.
And so it's like...
I'll just let them do it and it's like, okay, well, that's my address. Okay, go ahead. But you know what?
Yeah, and I'm but I'm listen I don't go as low as them at doxing if you want if you want the doxes
You know you go to QE farms. I mean all the information is on there, you know QE farms
It's kind of like I was a little bit leery of it because it's like oh, this is a doxing site
But then it's a site that actually
stands up for the truth in a certain way,
as in like, you know,
they don't think what the Kennel kickers does is right,
you know, and...
They think that it's like it's like this a moral selectiveness because they say candle pickers will say oh well
You know we were going after Gary Chapin because of the PDF and stuff
There's no PDF on Gary Chapin's record who's a blind man with a mental disabilities by the way who they had to go to Groovy
Jimmy's store asking for Gary Coleman who they sent a
Angry angry black guy to his house looking for a free laptop that fucking punched him in the face
There's actually a video with him with like all these welts and stuff on Oliver's face
You're not okay. It's okay if you're not a fan of it, but it's like, you know that in that situation
Okay, and also, you know that you know Alexander's on there too. Go look her up, too
Okay, you get the whole story. Okay, you get the whole story because there isn't good information there
And I don't think they go after people unless they really really deserve it
And it's like it's because it's like if they were because basically kettle kickers is trying to be like a version of that
But it's like kiwi farmers once nothing to do with them, right?
They think that they're they think that are disgusting because they go after people this they keep calling people pedophiles
Um, that are like, you know, like a 30 year old man and a 20 year old woman to consider that pedophilia over there, right?
It's just like they're saying. Oh, i'm a pdf because i like joker
We know ever friends with joker who's 26 years old and i'm 46 i'm going after people 20 years by mine or you know
Which is like just like i mean it's just so stupid right i mean it's like
I mean, you know, I'll even go to the far to say, you know, it's like, you know, basically on my show
I went to people 21 and over and stuff like that. It may be like even 18 is too young
I think to be participating in my show, right, but I
Don't know. It is crazy. It's crazy, right?
And so yeah, and so, you know, it mean it basically it's a website
Okay, and there's like, you know, the people on the website there's people that go too far about some things, right?
But there's also people that are just putting out the truth and also
I mean there is some justice in it. I would say because it's not as bad as the thought cited
I thought and you know what and I wasn't on that site
You know, I look I looked for my name and I know all this stuff, you know all and say I'm not on there
You know, it's like and you know, who is there it was on there? There's some people in this community that are on there
Okay, including this one guy Jimmy death
It's part of the kennel kickers, right and he was in the chat yesterday
Attacking me, right?
So anyway
You know, sorry, not sorry. I'm not doc. Sam. I'm directing you to maybe a site breaking in more information about these things if you are interested
Okay, I'm not gonna give out the exact URL of everything you're gonna go there search yourself
All you do is go search and look for the names. Okay, there's plenty of information available
You can see the history of these people. Okay
It's just sad. It's just sad, um, and I've been on for, you know, I'll stay on for a few more minutes.
I mean, I'd say, I guess, like, you know, guys, you know, if you want to go and I guess, you know,
Bea is still streaming and I guess Eldos, if anyone has, if Eldos is still streaming,
can someone post Eldos, um, link or his channel name, because I want to go over there and go on
the panel. I think I'll wrap it up here.
And I'll I'll just throw my left my newest video and then I'll like I'm you know if anyone has
Big Eldos channel you posted my chat. I just had trouble finding it and I'm gonna go over there
But we'll see so here's my newest video
Thanks for being here. I'll be on again tonight probably just having a couple drinks right now
Yeah, here you go
south bay signal late night code everybody wanting pieces of me smiles
with knives underneath I learned how the crowd consumes how applause can become
your tomb so I built my home from silence first watched fake kings rehearse their words